Jamie and Bo, where are you? Can you
stand up? Don't be shy. Jamie and
Bo.
Yeah. And your assistant. Your
assistant.
Yeah.
Uh, so they have a special website
called the knowledge base.
They put 5,000 videos on there and they
have 5,000 more they are fixing now. So
it's 10,000 videos and it's free and
they work very hard to make the
descriptions both working on the long
rim. She finished I think five courses.
I'm not sure. Am I right? Five courses.
Six courses. and uh she connected to the
original uh language and you know she
did all this work. She and her assistant
uh did all of this work. So the 14 years
of L room
uh you can you can watch uh 14 years for
free uh on the knowledge base. Let's
give them another
They always give me the same answer when
I we go out to dinner once a year, once
every 10 years, and uh I say, "You guys
need any money?" And they say, "No."
They're the only people who say no. And
uh they say, "No, we we don't need. We
Okay." And uh but they do take donation.
Okay. So uh if you watch the the classes
on their site, I encourage you to to
give some donation. They survive from
that. They don't ask me for money.
They're the only people that don't ask
me for money. So seriously. So so you
should help them. I hope. Okay. I took
them to dinner. I said no.
[Music]